A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A2, Groves House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A10, Staliper House (near access road), 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, View across field from 24-4-A2 Centreville Road looking south, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, View across field from 24-4-A2 Centreville Road looking south, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: no site, View across field from 24-4-A2 Centreville Road looking south, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-44, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A1, Dairy Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A10, Frying Pan Farm, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A18, Frying Pan Blacksmith Shop, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-45, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A1, Moore House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-46, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-47, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A10, Downe House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A4, Hagar House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A4, Hagar House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-48, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, Views of Dairy Barns across street 24-4-A3 29-258, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-49, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A4, Nickerson House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgartner(?) House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-50, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A4, Quillan House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A5, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A5, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A5, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A5, House, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A9, Barn/Corncrib, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A9, Barn/Corncrib, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A9, Barn/Corncrib, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-3-A1, Chantilly Baptist Church, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-3-A1, Chantilly Baptist Church, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-3-A1, Chantilly Baptist Church, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A1, Turley Hall, 1985 June; Roll #: 85-51, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #:, unidentified, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-52, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A7, Murphy Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A13, Coats House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist Church, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist Church, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist Church, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist Church, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist Church, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-53, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgarntner(?), 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A14, Baumgarntner(?), 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A13, Cockerill Farm, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A3, Billingsley House, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A4, Horsepen Run Bridge, 1985 July; Roll #: 85-54, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A4, Floris Methodist, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church (new church), 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church (new church), 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-56, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 13-1-A1, Old School House - Great Falls Post Office, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A1, Ayre House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-57, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 0000
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 44-1-A-2, Westfields #2, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 33-2-A8, Hutchison House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-2-A4, Everhard House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-58, Frame #: 021